<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Change notes on </title>
    <link>/docs/change_notes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Change notes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 15:37:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/change_notes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>V2.3.0</title>
      <link>/docs/change_notes/2.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 10:28:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/change_notes/2.3.0/</guid>
      <description>V2.3.0 Sakuli V2.3.0 comes with a lot of improvements in performance and stability as well as with a lot of bug fixes and a completely new forwarder integration. Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at the major changes for this release.
Sakuli Core Besides node 12 support and adjustments in Sakuli click actions, we&amp;rsquo;ve improved CLI output in case of check/test failures and added ways to ensure a stable website before performing any action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V2.4.0</title>
      <link>/docs/change_notes/2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 10:28:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/change_notes/2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>V2.4.0 Sakuli V2.4.0 brings new features but also a lot of improvements and bug fixes for enhanced user experience. Let&amp;rsquo;s have a look at the major changes for this release.
Sakuli Core Besides our brand-new preset autodiscovery a lot of improvements went into this release. Enhanced scroll behaviour, new config options and improvements for native interactions are just some of them. A detailed list of all applied enhancement and fixes can be found in the CHANGELOG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V2.5.0</title>
      <link>/docs/change_notes/2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 13:52:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/change_notes/2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>V2.5.0 Sakuli Core The new Sakuli Release 2.5.0 has many improvements in its luggage, which both users and developers have longed for. In addition, a completely new option for automation made it into the release! We are talking about the Sakuli OCR module. But everything in the right order! Let&amp;rsquo;s get it started with the improvements on the Sakuli core! A detailed list of all applied enhancement and fixes can be found in the CHANGELOG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>V3.0.0</title>
      <link>/docs/change_notes/3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Feb 2022 09:38:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/change_notes/3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>V3.0.0 Sakuli - Open Source All Enterprise Features are now open-source and can be used free of charge.
 Sakuli Forwarder Sakuli OCR Sakuli Docker Sakuli Docker Remote Connection Sakuli S2I Sakuli Dashboard  Node From now on, Sakuli also supports the latest LTS version of Node (v16.x, codename lts/gallium), so feel free to update your systems to the latest LTS version. We have updated our containers accordingly to run on lts/gallium as of 3.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>